{
    "id": "f8a02d81db064de98e631062e261aa6f",
    "title": "Possessives And Reflexives",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It is ................................ bag.",
            "description": "The possessive adjective is used before a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "mine",
                "myself"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2ef3ce27804c46ffae908a412ddc9a89"
        },
        {
            "question": "He injured ................................ while playing football.",
            "description": "When the subject and the object refer to the same person, the reflexive is used.",
            "answers": [
                "him",
                "himself",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a0778660cb9e4ad693da95d345afb2a7"
        },
        {
            "question": "She cooked dinner ......................................",
            "description": "The emphatic is used to emphasize an idea. ",
            "answers": [
                "herself",
                "hers",
                "her"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ace642b4708f436181f9e124f8f974ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "He snatched the paper from ........................................ hand.",
            "description": "The possessive adjective is used before a noun the possessive pronoun (mine, yours, ours etc.) is used alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "mine",
                "myself"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "64d9f6ea47cb47eaa4e0ab37a0718be0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can't believe ..................................... story.",
            "description": "The possessive adjective is used before a noun the possessive pronoun (mine, yours, ours etc.) is used alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "yourself",
                "yours",
                "your"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "730632feb1f0449580224043b5ad6ac5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw it with ....................................... own eyes.",
            "description": "The possessive adjective is used before a noun the possessive pronoun (mine, yours, ours etc.) is used alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "mine",
                "myself"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8767bf78376d4ea1a2fc508ab7964605"
        },
        {
            "question": "There was no one to help me so I had to do it .......................................",
            "description": "The emphatic pronoun is used to emphasize.",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "myself",
                "myselves"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a7acd31fccc34b2da0f55ebd006bd531"
        },
        {
            "question": "Someone broke into .......................................... house while we were away.",
            "description": "The possessive adjective is used before a noun the possessive pronoun (mine, yours, ours etc.) is used alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "us",
                "ourselves",
                "our"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "430bbdc034b94f0884dc7e89562533b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please do it ......................................",
            "description": "The emphatic pronoun is used to emphasize.",
            "answers": [
                "you",
                "yourself",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "afd860c6523b40519b022d82d39a07aa"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't think it is ....................................... responsibility.",
            "description": "The possessive adjective is used before a noun the possessive pronoun (mine, yours, ours etc.) is used alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "mine",
                "myself"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "115a97863bad4685b746ced1249a11df"
        },
        {
            "question": "Be careful or you will injure ........................................",
            "description": "When the subject and the object refer to the same person, the reflexive is used.",
            "answers": [
                "you",
                "yourself",
                "you itself"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e472de779d8d46f9a2a6514620579494"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is your fault, not ...........................................",
            "description": "The possessive adjective is used before a noun the possessive pronoun (mine, yours, ours etc.) is used alone. ",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "me",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "54f688f6cabc4f82840a1e2c1436bd24"
        }
    ]
}